紙牌屋
前情提要
翻譯   國士章魚X
翻譯   杏仁斯嘉麗
翻譯   吃冰棒
翻譯   蘇小黛
翻譯   肉松
翻譯   沫沫
時間軸   萌
時間軸   Ans
后期   餓得慌
顧問   老杜
校對   草草
總監   草草
紙牌屋
人人影視傾情奉獻
第五季  第八集
圣達菲縣
身份不明人員搜索
考察船
中國伸出援手  俄被困船員安全獲救
佐伊·巴恩斯
記者  媒體證
本杰明·格蘭特  他是波利跳的創始人
Benjamin Grant. He's the founder of Pollyhop,
很多大公司都不參與政治
A lot of big companies stay out of politics.
但波利跳不是如此
But not Pollyhop.
戴維斯女士  你有什么提議
Miss Davis. What are you offering?
我可以幫忙  總統女士
Help. Madam President.
他知道  你們不就是想知道這個嗎
He knew. Isn't that what you're all wondering?
您今天最沒想到會見到的就是我吧
I imagine I'm the last person you expected to see today.
你要讓我在南極洲任意開采石油
You will allow me to exploit whatever oil I find in Antarctica.
我告訴你為什么
And I'll tell you why.
我手上有料
I have something.
或者說有你們想要的人
Or rather, someone you need.
你的艾丹·麥卡倫
Your Aidan Macallan.
總統獲勝的可能性有多大
What are the president's chances?
田納西和俄亥俄的重投是他的最佳機會
The revote in Tennessee and Ohio is his best shot.
我一定會成為總統
I'm gonna be the president,
你也一定要把那該死的操縱桿給我
and you're going to flip me those motherfucking controls.
你會被稱為副總統
You'll be called vice president,
但實際上  你將做到更多
but you will be, de facto, something more.
我們得和厄舍談談
We need to sit down with Usher.
他這周末正好要去北加州
Just so happens, he's going to Northern California this weekend
見一幫人
to meet with a group of men
討論我們國家的危機和未來
to discuss the crisis and the future of our country.
本森法官的休會任命宣布儀式
The announcement of the recess appointment of Judge Benson
已經改到明天上午了
has been rescheduled for tomorrow morning.
那...我們可以進行選舉了
So... we have an election.
極樂圣鴉啊  我們崇敬你
Crow of Elysium, we honor thee!
我們崇敬你  我們崇敬你  我們崇敬你
We honor thee! We honor thee! We honor thee!
人間煙火燒不盡俗世煩惱
No mortal flame can destroy common woe.
唯有真火才能將其震懾
Just one fire can conquer.
那就是在極樂之地燃燒的真火
Fire that burns in the fields of Elysium.
致敬吧  弟兄們  眾弟兄
Hail, brothers! Many brothers!
兄弟為眾  乃成一心
Brothers many, make brothers one.
致敬吧  同胞  致敬降臨在翠綠王國的圣鴉
Hail, fellowship! Hail Crow in his verdant kingdom.
俗世煩惱啊  散去吧
Common woe, be done!
致敬吧  弟兄們  俗世煩惱啊  散去吧
Hail, brothers! Common woe, be done!
釋我自由  釋我自由
Set us free! Set us free!
釋我自由  釋我自由  釋我自由
Set us free! Set us free! Set us free!
釋我自由  釋我自由
Set us free! Set us free!
看看四周吧
Yeah... look around.
世界上最有權勢的一些人
Some of the most powerful men in the world
聚集在這片林間空地
are gathered in this clearing.
他們都是全國最難加入的俱樂部的成員
Members of one of our country's most exclusive clubs.
僅限邀請  當然了  除非你不請自來
Invitation only, unless, of course, you invite yourself.
他們在這里聚集  是想
They gather here to seek God
在參天大樹和綠林之間與上帝交心
between the branches of these magnificent trees.
他們一起吃喝  一起撒尿
They eat together, they piss next to each other,
就像周末烤肉一樣切割這世界
and they carve up the world like a Sunday roast.
真正的權力就在這里
This is where the real power is.
女人和總統禁止入內
No women or presidents allowed.
我不是前者  我將會再次成為后者
The former, I am not. The latter, I will be again,
因為我成功將一場全國大選
because I have managed to reduce
縮小到了一個州的競爭
a national election down to one state.
雖然讓這些人
And while these men here
左右全國的選票不太可能
can't swing the votes of an entire nation...
但區區一個小州
one measly state?
他們還是可以的  所以我才來到這里
Well, that they can do. And that's why I'm here.
那么  歡迎來到極樂之地
So welcome to Elysian Fields.
他不在  你是不是覺得很別扭
It's strange for you, isn't it? Without him here.
沒什么別扭的  夫人
It's not strange, ma'am.
莉安去辛辛那提敲定辯論的事了
LeAnn's in Cincinnati, trying to close the deal for the debate.
等總統回來  就巡回全州  出席多場
The president will make a series of appearances across the state
拉票活動
as soon as he gets back.
如果他能挺過這個周末  有消息嗎
If he survives the weekend. Anything?
那里不讓帶手機
No phones allowed.
我們這是分頭行動  各個擊破
Well, we're dividing and conquering.
這份對華貿易協定
This Chinese trade agreement
會讓俄亥俄州選民非常開心的
is going to make Ohio voters very happy.
能幫我們勝選
It could help us win.
-我不知道協議談妥了  -就快談妥了
- I didn't know the deal had closed. - Well, we're on the verge.
等總統到坎頓出席活動的時候可以當眾宣布
The president can make the announcement in Canton when he appears.
不用了  我自己宣布就行
Oh, no, I'll be announcing myself...
畢竟是我談定的
since I did the deal.
道格  你非常真誠
Doug, you are very sincere...
對弗蘭西斯也很忠誠
and very loyal to Francis.
我也忠于你  夫人
And loyal to you, ma'am.
我希望您知道這一點
I hope you know that.
其實你叫我克萊爾也是可以的
I don't mind it if you call me Claire, you know.
我這就帶戴維斯女士進來
I'll show Ms. Davis in.
你好啊  簡
Hi, Jane.
在會見部長之前  你能和我一起
Would you mind going over these numbers with me
再過一遍這些數字嗎
before we meet with the minister?
我知道中方嘴上能接受的數字
I have what China says they'll settle for,
也知道他們心里愿接受的數字
and what I know they'll settle for.
我想感謝你在這件事上給我們的幫助
And listen, I want to thank you so much for helping us with this.
我就想看到安德伍德執政
I'd like to see an Underwood administration.
道格  沒別的事了
Doug, that's all for now.
好的  夫人
Yes, ma'am.
-你可以給我看的  -我不想讓你看
- You can show me. - I don't want to.
你不用這么保護我
You don't have to protect me.
她們每個人背后都有一段故事
Each of them has a story.
就算她們后來迷失了
Even if they got lost somewhere.
消失比你想得要困難
It's harder to disappear than you would think.
但瑞秋
But Rachel...
完全不見蹤影
is nowhere.
這脖子我一眼就認出來了
I recognize that neck.
弗蘭克·安德伍德  真沒想到
Frank Underwood, as I live and breathe.
打賭你贏了
Well, I owe you this.
他不認為你會來
He didn't expect you to show up.
能見到老朋友總是很開心
I'm always happy to see old friends.
交新朋友也很開心  弗蘭克·安德伍德
And make new ones. Frank Underwood.
-本杰明·格蘭特  -波利跳的那位  是啊
- Benjamin Grant. - Oh, of Pollyhop. Of course.
你是我對手的強烈支持者
You're a big supporter of my opponent.
他是個高瞻遠矚的人  也是我朋友
He's a forward-thinking guy and a friend,
他現在應該是總統
who should be president right now.
先生們  在這兒的時候
There's no talking politics or business
不能談政治或生意
while we're here, gentlemen.
是啊  我們可別用爭吵荼毒了自然
Yes, we don't want to poison all this nature with words.
你知道這兒的口號
You know the motto.
是啊  "辛勤的蜜蜂別在這兒干活"
Yes, "Buzzing bees, sting not here."
想看不見都難
It's hard to miss.
泰德  這幾位你都認識吧
Ted, I think you know everybody.
俗世煩惱毫無勝算  總統先生
Common woe never stood a chance. Mr. President.
據我所知  這是你第一次受邀
First time you've been invited, I understand.
這句話里肯定有侮辱的意味  將軍
I'm almost sure there's an insult in there somewhere, General.
泰德和我
You know, Ted and I
剛剛在坎頓一家牛排店
just had the most remarkable piece of red meat
吃到了最好吃的紅肉
at a steak house out in Canton.
我記不清了  你喜不喜歡上等肋條
I can't remember, do you like prime rib?
要是有合適的人陪的話
In the right company.
先失陪了
If you'll excuse us,
泰德和我答應本杰明
Ted and I promised young Benjamin here
給他點一杯成人飲料
we'd find him an adult beverage.
-喝酒嗎  -還是不了
- Drink? - I'd rather not.
所有人都想跟將軍
You know, everybody was looking forward to
談幾句
spending some time with the general.
現在你也來了
And now you're here as well.
這個周末之后  誰知道呢
After this weekend, who knows?
也許這混蛋大選
Maybe this goddamn bastard of an election
能自行解決
will get itself resolved.
既然你來了
Oh, one little piece of advice
我還想給你一條小小的建議
that I could give you as long as you're out here.
要是你不招惹胡蜂  他們也不會惹你
If you don't bother the yellow jackets, they won't bother you.
你為什么不邀請康威
So why didn't you invite Conway?
被邀請的是布洛哈特
Brockhart was invited instead.
下周不會有辯論了  對吧
So there's not going to be a debate next week, is there?
不會有總統辯論
Not a presidential one, no.
我真應該在俄亥俄  跟人握手
I should really be in Ohio, shaking hands.
你可是費了好大勁進來的  弗蘭西斯
Yeah, you bargained to get in here, Francis,
既然你都來了  那我給你點建議
and now you're here. So let me suggest something.
去他的俄亥俄
Fuck Ohio.
這就是競選
This is the campaign.
將軍是個叛徒  這你清楚
The general is a traitor, you know that.
將軍想當個政客
The general is trying to be a politician.
換成你也會這么做
You would have done the same.
對  但做得更高明
Yeah, but better.
安德伍德總統
President Underwood?
安德伍德總統  抱歉  女士
President Underwood? I'm sorry, ma'am,
但戰況室急需你過去
but you're needed in the Situation Room.
凱茜
Cathy.
進屋之前  我想先跟你說句話
I wanted a moment with you before we join the rest of the team.
-來的路上他們已經跟我說明了  -說得不全
- Oh, I was briefed on the way over. - Not fully.
一艘俄羅斯考察船受困  在下沉
A Russian research vessel is stuck and sinking--
對  他們聲稱是在采集冰芯樣本
Yes, they claim they were taking core samples,
全球變暖那套屁話
some global warming nonsense.
但他們其實是在勘探石油
But they were looking for oil.
他們發出了求救信號
There was a distress signal
然后通訊就完全中斷了
and then all communication just shut down.
我們是附近唯一能發起救援的國家
We're the only country in position to rescue.
所以20分鐘前  我們向他們提出援救
So, 20 minutes ago, we offered.
-他們不接受  -而且拒不承認
- They declined? - And denied.
佩特羅夫不希望我們知道船上有什么
Petrov does not want us to see what's on board.
我明白這決定很難做
I understand this is a difficult decision,
但人命關天
but there are human lives at stake,
如果救援隊抵達
and if help arrives,
-佩特羅夫只能被迫接受  -好吧
- Petrov will be forced to take it. - Okay.
謝謝  我得直接和佩特羅夫總統通話
Well, thank you. I need to speak with President Petrov directly.
海上救援  給你機會羞辱我們嗎
A rescue at sea and a chance to embarrass us?
而且就在第二次大選日前夕
Just before your second Election Day?
感覺更像是我幫你  對嗎
Sounds like I would be helping you, hmm?
船一沉  你的船員就會死
The boat sinks, your crew dies.
俄羅斯國內輿論會怎么樣
How is that going to look at home?
我讓我的人民怎么想  他們就會怎么想
I tell my people how things look, and that's how they look.
我想給你看個東西
I want to show you something.
稍等
Wait a minute.
這個  你喜歡我的樣子嗎
There. Do you like my face?
你不適合留胡子
A beard doesn't suit you.
不知你的人民會對你做的事有何感想
I wonder how your citizens would feel about what you've done.
我可以把你們的船員送回俄羅斯  維克多
I could return your crew to Russia, Viktor.
你把艾丹·麥卡倫還給我們
You could return Aidan Macallan.
我不喜歡量化人的價值
I don't like to quantify human worth...
但麥卡倫的價值確實更高
but Macallan's is higher.
社交媒體是個強大的工具
Social media is a powerful tool.
如果美國采取任何救援措施
If there is any rescue attempt by the United States,
我就告訴俄亥俄州的人民你的真面目
I will tell the people of Ohio exactly how you look to them.
告訴他們你是如何破壞他們州的選舉的
Exactly how you disrupted their state's vote.
他們會相信我的
And they will believe me.
奧本海默也曾是成員
Oppenheimer was a member.
那邊那棵樹
That tree right over there,
曼哈頓計劃就是誕生在那棵樹下
right under that tree, Manhattan Project was born.
而我在這顆樹下小解
And right under this one, I'm relieving myself.
希望你不是把我和原子彈畫上等號
I hope you're not equating me to the atom bomb.
你想要什么  內閣職位
What do you want? Cabinet position?
-弗蘭克·安德伍德  -司法任命
- Frank Underwood-- - Judicial appointments?
-支持你的法案  -勿談公事  勿談公事
- Legislative support? - Ah, buzzing bees, buzzing bees.
對哦  因為曼哈頓計劃
Oh, right. Because the Manhattan Project
和商業或政治
had absolutely nothing to do
-毫無關系  -我希望你放松
- with business or politics. - I want you to breathe.
我希望你看看月光穿過樹稍的景色
I want you to look how the moonlight cuts through the trees.
弗蘭西斯  好好利用這次機會
Take this time, Francis,
了解一下其他人
to know your other attendees.
想想你究竟想做一名什么樣的總統
Think about what kind of president you really want to be.
這樣又如何
What am I supposed to do with that?
就是...
Just...
你就是這么跟將軍說的嗎
Oh, is that what you told the general?
抗命
Insubordination.
密謀叛變
Clandestine coup.
對  這才是真正的領袖
Oh, yes, that's the stuff of real leadership.
有錢人喜歡軍人
People with money like uniforms.
馬克  告訴我他們想要什么
Mark, just tell me what they want.
他們在等你
They're waiting for you.
你起得真早  總統先生
You're up early, Mr. President.
習慣了
Always.
你餓嗎  我有雞蛋
Are you hungry? I have, uh, eggs,
還有橙汁  山蛤蜊
and orange juice, mountain oysters.
你說的是牛睪丸  對嗎
You mean bull's testicles, don't you?
我喜歡叫它們的本名
I prefer to call things what they are.
出人意料啊
This is unexpected.
我以為你會一直忙著競選的事
I thought you'd stay out there campaigning
直到最后一口氣
till your dying breath.
怎么  把你們丟在這荒山野嶺
What, and leave you out here all alone in the wilderness
去做那些重要的決策嗎
to make all these important decisions?
我以前待你不薄  雷蒙德  我希望你支持我
You've done well by me, Raymond. I'd like your support.
是你妻子待我不薄
I've done well by your wife.
而她現在又正好是掌管白宮的人
Who happens, at this moment, to rule the White House.
別跟我說你是想拿你妻子來賄賂我
Tell me you're not peddling influence with your wife?
你是說現在的美國代總統嗎
Who, you mean the current acting President of the United States?
也就再做兩周吧
For the next two weeks.
稍有收斂  那才讓人出乎意料呢
A little restraint? Now, that... that would be unexpected.
你的雞蛋想怎么吃
How do you like your eggs?
下午再吃
In the afternoon.
早上好  總統先生
Good morning, Mr. President.
在極樂之地可沒有總統  不是嗎
Oh, no presidents here at Elysian Fields, isn't that right?
只有前任的  或者將來的
Only former ones... or future.
我不會把這稱為政治  這只是時事
Well, I won't call this politics, then. Just current affairs.
我們有過很好的機會拿下艾哈邁迪
We had a real chance to get Ahmadi.
我們的團隊收到簡報了
Our campaign was briefed.
你們知道得要更詳細些吧
I think a little more than just briefed.
你有多的襪子嗎  雷蒙德
Do you have an extra pair of socks, Raymond?
服了30年的兵役
After 30 years of military service,
按說我該自己備好呢
you'd think I'd arrive prepared.
這里肯定有人能幫你找一雙[膽子]
Oh, I'm sure someone around here could find you a pair.
-我的鋪位下面有  -謝謝
- Under my bunk. - Thank you.
他是個好人
He's a good man.
很難找到不信任或不喜歡他的人
Hard to find anybody who distrusts or dislikes him.
你到底要不要雞蛋
So do you want eggs or not?
以這個關稅率
With this rate of tariff,
我有信心會對反傾銷案例
I'm confident it'll have a mitigating effect
起到減震作用
on the anti-dumping cases.
我覺得這能行
I think this is going to work.
我得向我國外交部國務委員請示
I'll need to run this by my State Councilor for Foreign Affairs.
我認為今天對我們兩國都是個好日子
I think this is a very good day for both of our countries.
是的
Yes, it is.
船上有個美國人
There's an American on the boat.
那艘俄羅斯的考察船上
The Russian research vessel.
-你怎么知道的  -你進來前徐先生告訴我的
- And how do you know that? - Mr. Xu told me before you came in.
我需要證據
I will need proof of that fact.
當然  但我們告訴你
Of course, but we are only telling you
只是因為我們知道你們會想援救他
because we know you'll want to rescue him.
中方愿在力所能及的范圍內盡量幫忙
And China is willing to help in any way we can.
我很好奇  徐先生
I'm just curious, Mr. Xu,
你為何如此關注這一情況
why are you so focused on this situation?
出于人道主義原因
For humanitarian reasons.
謝謝您的時間和合作  代總統女士
Thank you for your time and cooperation, Madam Acting President.
這是必要條件
It's contingent.
如果希望部長繼續關稅交易
The minister won't proceed with our tariff deal
我們必須向他保證  救援已經開展
if we don't give him assurances that the rescue is underway.
中方為何如此關心
Why do the Chinese care so much
這艘俄羅斯船上有什么
about what's on this Russian boat?
不知道  我自己也是剛知道
I don't know. I was just informed myself.
他們在合作嗎
Are they working together?
再說一次  我不知道
Again, I don't know.
你在跟他們合作嗎
Are you working with them?
我跟誰都合作
I work with everybody.
但這不是重點  關鍵是船上有個美國人
But that's beside the point. There is an American on board.
你相信嗎
And you believe that?
你可不想做出錯誤的決定
Well, you wouldn't want to make the wrong call.
公牛的睪丸
Bull's balls.
一只大烏鴉
A giant crow.
還有百萬富翁們呼喊著  "釋我自由"
And billionaires chanting, "Set me free."
這地方真是把我無法言表的感覺都呈現出來了
Well, this place says everything I feel, but can't express.
他不可能是你的朋友
He can't be your friend.
塔斯克沒有朋友
Tusk doesn't have any friends.
他是個...伙伴
He's, uh, an associate.
是嗎
Really?
他跟你有什么伙伴關系
And how does he associate with you?
別管那該死的蜜蜂了  沒人在意它
Oh, to hell with the buzzing bees. No one else is heeding it.
一個電視臺總裁  一個電信首席執行官
A network president, a telecom CEO,
還有一個副總統候選人
the vice presidential candidate.
你覺得他們都在聊什么
What do you think they're all talking about,
-他們最近看的書嗎  -你又在看什么
- the last book they read? - What are you reading?
你的臉
Your face...
它讓我知道了你有多不想待在這里
which tells me how much you don't want to be here.
塔斯克先生曾是威爾競選的主要捐助者
Mr. Tusk was a major donor on Will's campaign.
嗯  所以他沒受邀  這很有趣
Yes, so it's interesting that he wasn't invited.
我們在合作一個項目
We're partnering on a project.
沙漠里的大規模數據存儲中心
Large-scale data storage centers in the desert.
太陽能的
Solar-powered.
我得去準備我的演講
I need to get ready for my talk.
《來世: 我們留下的》
"The Life After: What We Leave Behind."
但愿你會出席
Hope you'll be there.
你聞聞
Smell that.
高斯巴雪茄
Cohiba.
我知道你很喜歡
I know you're a fan.
雖然我不抽了  但不代表我不能...
Even though I don't smoke anymore, doesn't mean I can't--
誰組織的這周末的聚會  你嗎
Who called this weekend's gathering? You?
不是  是塔斯克
No. Tusk did.
怎么
Why?
我們覺得中國人說得對  船上的確有一位美國人
We think the Chinese are right. There is an American on board.
這是撒德·彼得森  兩年前退休了
This is Thad Peterson. Retired two years ago.
地球物理研究主任
Director of geophysics research
在美國幾家頂尖石油公司供職
for some of the country's top oil companies.
我們強烈懷疑他在那艘船上
We strongly suspect he's on board the boat.
正在和俄羅斯人合作
Working with the Russians.
證據呢
Where's the proof?
這是通訊中斷前
This was sent from a Russian sailor's cell phone
俄羅斯船員的手機發出的
before communications were cut off.
打開無線電求救
Get on the radio and call for help!
他的妻子確認
His wife confirmed that
錄音里就是撒德·彼得森的聲音
this is Thad Peterson's voice on the recording.
24小時后  最多36小時  那艘船就會沉
In 24, 36 hours tops, that boat's gone.
對  但那不能證明撒德·彼得森在船上
Yes, but that doesn't prove that Thad Peterson was on the ship.
但女士  他是美國人
But, ma'am... he is an American--
不  我們不能確定  除非有乘客名單
No, we can't be sure until we have a passenger manifest.
等有更多信息再開會
Let's reconvene when you know more.
-怎么了  凱茜  -你決定不干預
- What is it, Cathy? - Your decision not to intervene.
如果有美國人在非法工作
If an American is working illegally,
他不會出現在名單上
he will not be on the manifest--
我還沒做決定  我在等更多信息
I haven't made a decision. I'm waiting for more information.
這關系到了艾丹·麥卡倫
This is about Aidan Macallan.
我非常確信
I am very confident
中國謊稱有美國人在船上
China is lying about an American being on board.
船上有他們想要的東西
There is something on that boat they want
得等我知道是什么再說
and I can't proceed until I know what it is.
他們說自己的動機是救人
They say they're motivated by saving human lives.
但那不是他們的真實動機
But that's not what's driving them.
我只是覺得難以接受
And I just find it so frustrating
人命受到如此漠視
when human life is treated with such disregard.
抱歉  但...
We're sorry. But...
俗話說的"林間漫步"不適合我
The proverbial walk in the woods is not for me.
在林蔭小徑尋尋覓覓
Navel-gazing on some forest path.
思考死亡與永生
Contemplating mortality. Immortality.
才不  歷史要去爭取
No. History is earned.
贏了今天  然后再去贏明天
You win the day, and then you win the day after,
日復一日  至死方休
and you do the same thing every day until you're dead.
你被載入史冊  不是因為你總贏
And you're remembered not for the winning,
而是因為你從不輸
but because you never lost.
好了
Now...
道格
Doug?
道格  能聽到嗎
Doug, can you hear me?
我現在需要些籌碼
I need some leverage out here right now.
-怎么了  -康威完了
- What's going on? - Conway is finished.
如果他們勝選
If they win,
布洛哈特會操控大局
Brockhart will do all the heavy lifting.
他會成為真正的總統
He'll essentially be the president.
我們該利用對手研究信息
We should have used the oppo.
聽著  布洛哈特是塔斯克挑的人
Listen, Brockhart is Tusk's pick.
我得找辦法逼那老頭支持我
I need to find a way to force that old man to support me.
-先生  總統先生  -聽得到嗎
- Sir? Mr. President? - Do you hear me?
我在聽
I'm here.
塔斯克和波利跳達成了交易
Tusk has some deal with Pollyhop.
我需要想辦法阻止他們
I need to find a way to stop that.
發個行政命令
An executive order...
先生
Sir?
稍有收斂
A little restraint...
那才讓人出乎意料
would be unexpected.
總統先生
Mr. President?
-道格  -先生
- Doug. - Sir?
什么都別做
Don't do anything.
我不明白
I don't understand.
什么都別做  等我的指令
Don't do anything until you hear from me.
-先生  波利跳交易怎么辦  -聽見了嗎
- Sir, what about the Pollyhop deal? - Do you hear me?
-什么都別...  -總統先生  我
- Don't do anything... - Mr. President, I...
你打回去了嗎
Have you tried calling him back?
沒人接  我們該做什么
There's no answer. What should we do?
什么都不做  總統既然說了  那就聽他的
Nothing. That's what the president said, so that's what we'll do.
-讓護衛把他撤出來嗎  -不  我們等著
- Should we have his team pull him out? - No. We wait.
夫人
Ma'am...
-如果我們沒能妥當處置營救的事  -道格
- if we don't handle this rescue correctly... - Doug.
讓我想辦法讓總統和佩特羅夫通上電話
Let me find a way to get the president on the phone with Petrov.
不  弗蘭西斯不需要分心
No. Francis doesn't need this distraction.
我不同意
I disagree.
我知道你不同意
I know you do.
人說三代之后就沒人會記得我們了
They say we're only remembered for three generations.
那一個人該做些什么才能不被忘卻呢
What would one have to do not to be forgotten?
小本杰明知道未來是啥樣
Young Benjamin here knows what's coming.
誰在乎他沒聽說過約翰尼·卡森[主持人]
Who cares if he's never heard of Johnny Carson?
可憐的老塔斯克
Poor old Tusk.
別看他嬉皮笑臉的  但他可騙不了我
He wears that game face, but he doesn't fool me.
未來讓他恐懼  因為他知道自己時日無多
The future terrifies him because he knows it's short.
聲明一下  我知道約翰尼·卡森是誰
For the record, I have heard of Johnny Carson.
他每天晚上哄我爸媽上床
He tucked my parents into bed every night.
我今天得到了特別的許可
I've been given special permission
向大家展示我們的成果
to show you what we've been working on.
想象這樣一種可能  你的大腦  你的意識
Imagine the possibility of your brain, your consciousness,
都實時進行數字化存儲
stored digitally in real time.
永生究竟是什么
I mean, what is immortality?
終有一日  格蘭特的設想也會過時
In time, even Grant's vision will get old.
早晚的事  誰都免不了
It will happen, as it does for all of us.
這還只是早期版本
Now this is still in the early stages,
但我們一直在收集儲存
but we've been collecting and storing
雷蒙德的記憶  想法  怪癖和愛好
Raymond's memories, thoughts, quirks and tics.
這還只是實驗版本  但最終
This is a mock-up. But eventually...
這個雷蒙德
this Raymond...
會像各位眼前這位一樣活生生
will feel as real as the one standing before you.
我更喜歡腳踏實地
I like dirt and rocks...
貨真價實
and facts.
這我也同意
No argument here.
我只相信能抓在手里的  或者能親眼看到的
I trust only what I can hold in my hand or see on my horizon.
但你不能光干坐著看風景啊
Well, but you can't just sit back and admire the view.
我就發現一定要緊抓當下
I've learned you've got to grab the present by the balls.
那才是美國人民在乎的
That's where the American people live.
你更像個推銷員而不是總統  總統先生
You sound more like a salesman than a president, Mr. President.
我們是美國人  我們就是推銷員
Well, if we're Americans, then we are salesmen, right?
這是我們天生的權利
That's our birthright.
賣車  賣手機  賣汽油
Cars and phones and a gallon of gas.
我眼里的美國可不是這樣
That's not how I see America.
我是愛國者  我為國效力
I'm a patriot. I serve.
那我們向你致敬  將軍
Well, then, we salute you, General.
但你為國效力的意義是什么
But you serve to what purpose?
不還是為了其他美國人能去推銷
So the rest of America can sell.
你看  這個周末  你和我
I mean, you and I, right now, this weekend,
不就在這個營地推銷自己嗎
we're here at this camp selling ourselves.
人的品質不言自明
Character speaks for itself.
人民需要一個他們能信賴的總統
People want a president they can trust.
錯  不對  他們需要一個他們了解的總統
No, they don't. They want a president they know.
而我也了解他們
And I know them.
我唯一感興趣的未來就是接下來的四年
The only future I'm interested in is the next four years.
所以沒錯  我明天要推銷  后天接著推銷
So, yes, I'm selling tomorrow and the day after that
大后天還要推銷
and the day after that.
我是在推銷一個曾經住在桃子農場的男孩
I'm selling a boy who used to live on a peach farm
而他現在住在白宮
who now lives in the White House.
我要推銷一個
I'm selling a tomorrow
可觸可感的明天
that you can see and touch and feel.
要是你把這個奪走
Now, you take that away,
我不知道這國家還剩下什么
and I don't know what this country has left.
只剩下一群成年男人
Except a group of grown men
圍成一圈  盯著一小塊屏幕
standing around in a circle, all staring at a small screen.
只向內看  而不往外面看
Looking in instead of looking out.
那隨時給我蓋一把黃土吧
Heck, give me a peck of dirt any day of the week.
說得好  敬黃土
Hear, hear. To a peck of dirt.
-說得好  -我要敬這一杯
- Hear, hear. - I will drink to that,
也要敬將軍一杯  他是位優秀的公仆
but I will also drink to the general, a good servant.
敬將軍
To the general.
我敢肯定  這一交易隨時可能落空
I promise you, this deal is on the verge of falling apart.
就在重新投票之前
Right before your revote.
我只是個傳話的
I... I'm only the messenger, by the way.
我們不能讓這筆交易落空
We can't let this deal fall apart.
沒錯  但我們必須馬上救援
Agreed. But the rescue has to happen immediately.
你好像跟這事有利益關系
You seem personally invested in this.
不不  我只是在尋找解決方案
Oh, no, no. I'm just looking for a solution.
我有個想法
I had a thought.
我愿意讓駐扎在喬治王島的
I would be willing to allow the Chinese sailors
中國船員登上我們的破冰船
that are stationed on King George Island to board our icebreaker.
然后  在內部攝像機前
Then, purely for the in-house cameras,
擺出是中國領導了此次救援的樣子
we let it appear as though the Chinese led the rescue.
當然  自始至終
Now, of course, the whole time,
都會是美國控制船
the Americans would remain in charge of the boat,
但不必讓俄羅斯人知道我們參與了
but the Russians don't need to know our involvement.
我覺得這是可以接受的
I imagine that would be acceptable.
我馬上就向徐先生轉達
I'll relay this scenario to Mr. Xu immediately.
我還想把關稅湊整成20%
But I'd also like to round up the tariff to 20%.
我們已經商定19%了
We have a firm deal at 19.
我知道  但突然間  這似乎不夠高
I know. But suddenly, it just doesn't seem high enough.
我覺得他們會答應的
I think they'll be okay with it.
祈禱如此吧  我盡力
Fingers crossed. I'll do my best.
-還挺順利的  -是啊  非常順利
- That went rather well, I think. - It did. It went very well.
你超出了所有人的預料
You've exceeded everyone's expectations,
整個周末你的表現很出色  但是
the way you handled yourself all weekend, but...
他們能預料布洛哈特的一舉一動
Brockhart's someone they can predict.
話先別說太早  這事還沒完
Don't get ahead of yourself. This is not over.
你要干什么  弗蘭西斯  你要利用對手研究嗎
What are you gonna do, Francis? Are you gonna use the oppo?
你似乎很著急嘛
Well, it seems to have worried you enough.
他還只是副總統候選人
He's still only the vice presidential candidate.
我要走了
I'm leaving.
-你不用走的  -我知道  什么都不是必須的
- You don't have to go. - No, I know. I don't have to do anything.
你記得我們第一次見面的情景吧
Do you remember when we first met?
你差一點就加入我第二次競選了
You almost joined my second campaign.
我們坐在加夫尼的便宜館子里
We sat down at that little greasy spoon in Gaffney.
記得  要是你招了我  肯定就大獲全勝了
Yeah, if you'd signed me on, you would have won by a landslide.
我還是贏了  因為我從不輸
I won anyway, because I never lose.
你知道當時我為什么沒雇你嗎
You know why I didn't hire you back then?
因為你去結賬的時候
Because when you went to pick up the check,
你告訴我不用給你錢
you told me I didn't have to pay you.
你愿意不要報酬為我工作  我不信
That you would work for free. I don't trust that.
因為誰也不會不要報酬
Because no one works for free.
總統女士  恐怕我不能同意20%
Madam President, I'm afraid I can't agree to 20%.
-對經濟的影響  -我們陷入僵局了
- The economic implications-- - We're at an impasse.
我很希望能繼續對話  但與此同時
I'm willing to keep the conversation going, but in the meantime--
你們不同意  我們就不行動
We'll do nothing until you agree.
總統女士  會有人喪命的
Madam President, people will die.
所以我才驚訝你居然不同意我的條件
Which is why I'm surprised you won't agree to my terms.
除非外交部國務委員同意
I can't agree to the terms without the approval
否則我不能同意你的條件
of my State Councillor for Foreign Affairs.
船上有112人
There are 112 people aboard the vessel.
要是算上彼得森先生就是113人
113 if you count Mr. Peterson.
20至32小時后  船就會完全沉沒
Now, it will go under in 20 to 32 hours.
現在南冰洋的水溫
The temperature of the Southern Ocean right now
是零下2攝氏度
is 28 degrees Fahrenheit.
在這么冷的水里  人不到45分鐘
A body will freeze to death within 45 minutes
就會凍死
in water that cold.
更不要說在凍死之前早就失去游泳能力了
And, of course, one loses the ability to swim long before that.
徐部長  你還在嗎
Minister Xu, are you still there?
和佩特羅夫總統合謀永遠是個錯誤
Collaborating with President Petrov is always a mistake.
20%的關稅會幫你們長長記性
The 20% tariff will help you keep that in mind.
我等你回復
I'm waiting.
這些人的死活取決于你了
It's up to you if they live or die.
-船員呢  -全部獲救
- The crew? - All rescued.
撒德·彼得森呢
And Thad Peterson?
你猜的沒錯  中國人在撒謊
You were right. The Chinese were lying.
只有他仍然下落不明
He's the only one still unaccounted for.
上將說還有機會拯救那艘船
The admiral says there's still a chance to save the boat.
讓它沉吧
Let it go down.
那佩特羅夫放在船上的東西呢
And whatever Petrov has on it?
我們這么做是對的  凱茜
We're doing the right thing, Cathy.
你已經達到目的了  維克多
You got what you wanted, Viktor.
船已經沉了  讓我們接著往下談吧
The boat is gone. Now let's get back to where we left off.
你想要什么  才能換艾丹·麥卡倫回國
What will it take to get Aidan Macallan back on American soil?
他挺喜歡這里的
He likes it here.
要走了嗎  總統先生
Leaving, Mr. President?
先放車上吧  謝謝
You can put that in the car, thank you.
-你沒事吧  -好多了
- Are you all right? - Better now.
你喝醉了
Are you drunk?
-來一口嗎  -不了
- You want a pull? - No.
我討厭這地方
I hate this place.
這些人
These men.
一個個仗著特權  趾高氣揚
Their privilege, their presumption.
和塔斯克的交易就是個錯誤
The deal with Tusk was a mistake.
你知道嗎
Do you know...
雷蒙德想把自己凍起來
Raymond wants to be frozen?
封進冰里  等將來再解凍
Put on ice until a later date.
-我要走了  -威爾·康威是我的朋友  但
- I have to get going. - Will Conway's my friend. But...
如果他贏了  不會有什么好結果的
this won't end well for him if he wins.
你照顧好自己  本
You take care of yourself, Ben.
他們有段他的錄音
They have a recording of him.
我馬上就過去
I'll be right there in a minute.
你必須向我保證
You have to promise me
威爾·康威絕不能知道是我給你的
Will Conway never finds out this came from me.
你知道我會成為總統吧
You know I'm gonna be the president, right?
-希望如此  先生  -你希望如此
- I hope so, sir. - You hope so?
我只是說我支持你  先生
I just mean I'm pulling for you, sir.
我一定會成為總統
I'm gonna be the president,
你也一定要把那該死的操縱桿給我
and you're going to flip me those motherfucking controls.
先生
Sir!
這肯定是飛行員錄的
I think this must have been recorded by the pilot.
我們應該先發給MSNBC和CNN
We should go to MSNBC and CNN first.
-我們可以大范圍傳播  -不  先等等
- We can go wide. - No, let's wait.
弗蘭西斯  你也聽到了
Francis, you heard what I heard.
所以留到明天效果一樣好
And it'll be just as good tomorrow.
讓道爾來核實  明天早上見
Have Doyle confirm it. I'll see you in the morning.
為什么不現在動手
Why not do it now?
我們要等總統回來
We need to wait for the president.
新聞持續關注
Stories are still swirling
中國在南冰洋對一艘俄考察船船員
around the events leading up to a daring Chinese-led rescue
展開的英勇救援行動
of the crew of a Russian research ship
該考察船被困在南極半島海岸冰層
stuck in ice for almost four days off the coast
長達四天之久
of the Antarctic Peninsula.
雖然該船最終沉沒  但船員全部獲救
Although the ship was lost, every crew member was saved.
俄羅斯總統維克多·佩特羅夫
Russian President Viktor Petrov
于今日上午向中國政府表達了由衷的感謝
expressed his gratitude to the Chinese government this morning.
看來兩位候選人終于精力不濟
Exhaustion must be catching up with the candidates,
安德伍德總統和他的競選搭檔周末休息
as President Underwood and his running mate took the weekend off.
布洛哈特將軍也不知所蹤
General Brockhart was nowhere to be seen,
只有康威州長
while only Governor Conway
在克利夫蘭地區短暫露面了兩次
made a pair of quick appearances in the Cleveland area.
那自來水會要你命的
That tap water is gonna kill you.
還有更糟的死法
There are worse ways to go.
我要坦白一件事
I have a confession.
你做了什么
What'd you do?
你在紐約時  我有時讓人監視你
I've had somebody watch you sometimes when you go to New York.
她叫凱倫
Her name's Karen.
她是誰
Who is she?
我覺得你沒資格問這個
I don't know you get to ask that.
她是我以前的老師
She was my teacher.
教過我神學和一些別的
Theology, among other things.
我不知我為什么那么做
I don't know why I did that.
不是因為嫉妒
It's not... about jealousy.
其實  她救過我的命
She saved my life, actually.
我很高興
I'm glad.
我們短時間內不會再見到凱倫了
Well, we won't be seeing Karen for a while.
她懂我  她看得出我對你的感覺
She knows me. She could see how I feel about you.
女士  這是初步協議
Ma'am, an initialed agreement.
那船上到底有什么  簡
What exactly was on that boat, Jane?
中國和俄羅斯
Uh, the Chinese and the Russians
獲取了一項他們不該有的技術
had access to technology they shouldn't have
又不想失去
and didn't want to lose.
現在他們失去了
And now they've lost it.
你有什么沒告訴我的
What aren't you telling me?
你想從中得到什么
What did you want out of all of this?
我告訴過你我想要什么
I told you what I wanted.
我想要那美國人離開那艘船
I wanted that American off the boat.
他就是那項技術
He was the technology.
來  給我
Here, give me that.
走吧
Go.
湯姆·漢默施密特
Tom Hammerschmidt.
警探  我拿到盤了
Detective, I got the drive.
還沒有  我剛放進電腦
Uh, no, I just put it in.
時間標識是
And... the time stamp says
2013年11月3日晚8:13
November 3rd, 2013, 8:13 p.m.
等一下
Hold on a second.
你沒事吧
You all right?
沒事  我要出去一下
Yeah. I just need to get out for a minute.
我在
I'm here.
我知道  我知道你忙
I know. I know you're busy.
感謝無以言表  我...
And I can't thank you enough, I...
我看看
Let me back you up a bit.
好  這是她死前兩天的錄像
Okay, so this is two days before she died.
州長聽起來精神錯亂了
The governor sounds unhinged.
不過我不太安心
It bothers me, though.
這也來得太容易了  你不覺得嗎
It came too easy, don't you think?
是的  但如果用上它  我們就能贏
Yes, but if we use it, we'll win.
我不知道  克萊爾  你了解這些人
I don't know, Claire. You know these types of people.
你要是在場就好了
You should have been there.
他們為什么要給我
Why would they hand me...
他就那么交給我了 為什么呢
He just handed me this. Why?
他們從不希望我當選  從一開始就是
When they've never wanted me, not from the beginning,
不論我怎么做
no matter what I do!
-讓他們見鬼去  -我正有此意
- Fuck 'em. - I intend to.
那你打算怎么做
And how do you intend to do that?
我要回來工作了
I'm going back to work.
我們很高興你能來
We're glad you came.
聽說這種周末活動過后得緩上一陣
I hear those weekends can, uh, take some recovery time.
我得說  我沒想到這么快就會再來
I must say, I didn't expect to be back here so soon.
馬克  我們再次請你來是因為
Well, Mark, we asked you back here because...
我們又拿到了一份錄音
we've come into possession of a second audio recording
是你的候選人在飛機上說的話
of your candidate on an airplane.
-他在錄音里說...  -我知道他說了什么
- He's been recorded saying... - I know what he said.
我當時在場
I was there.
不知我們能否商討一下
So, we were wondering if we can discuss how...
我們可以如何合作
we might be able to work together.
我們三個人能實現很多成果
We can accomplish a great deal. The three of us.
在你說話前
Now, before you say anything,
我先說說這場談話會如何進行
let me tell you how this conversation's going to go.
你會說到黨派忠誠
You're going to talk about party loyalty,
我會說你的候選人有多差勁
and I'm going to talk about how weak your candidates are
你其實別無選擇
and that you really have no choice.
然后你會說你們還能贏下俄亥俄州
And then you're going to say that your ticket can still win Ohio.
接著我會說"不  贏不了"
And I'm going to say, "No, they can't."
但這場談話中不會談到
But what's going to go unsaid in this conversation
我和克萊爾
is that Claire and I...
愿意不惜一切
are willing... to do anything.
我們知道
And we know...
你也如此
that you are no different.
好吧  我可以先為你倆安排一些會面
Okay, I can start by setting up some meetings for both of you.
當然不能公開行動
I can't do that publicly, of course.
我建議你們慢慢抖出手上的料
I suggest you release whatever you have slowly.
一次一條
One at a time.
讓事情發酵
Let's make this build.
消息一曝光
Once it gets out,
我會確保共和黨人
I'll make sure the Republicans
不會維護我的候選人
don't come to my candidate's defense.
我當時的情況很糟
I was in a really bad place.
什么都做不了
I couldn't do anything.
無法離開我的公寓
I couldn't leave my apartment.
為什么
Why?
這種事的發生  很莫名
It's mysterious, isn't it, when these things happen?
或許你沒遇到過
Or maybe it never happened to you.
但我有一天醒來  感覺好像...
But I woke up one day and it felt like...
我考慮要做的一切
everything I contemplated doing, everything,
從去咖啡店
from going to the coffee shop...
到看一本書  寫一章書  就是很...
to... reading a book, writing a chapter, it was just...
可笑
laughable.
什么意思
As in?
就是  沒有意義
As in... pointless.
但多虧了凱倫
And Karen, bless her...
她幫我找到了意義  不是找到
she helped me find a point. Or, not find one.
而是發現找到意義的可能性
Realize the possibility of one.
你們當時在一起嗎
Were you together?
沒錯  我們還結了婚
Yeah. We were married.
大概三年  都是陳年舊事
For about three years. A million years ago.
她人很好
She's a good person.
她只是...現在狀況不太好  所以我想幫她
She's just... having a hard time. So I'm trying to help her.
找到意義
Find a point?
你經歷過那種低谷嗎
You ever been that dark?
我想和你在一起
I wanna be with you.
我愛你
I love you.
我也許也愛你
I think I might love you, too.
這是30秒宣傳片的稿子
That's the script for the 30-second spot.
我們不想下手太重
We don't wanna hit him too hard.
不然可能被當成落井下石
There's a risk of kicking him while he's down.
誰上晨間節目
Who's doing the morning shows?
朋友  他們會禮貌地質疑康威的勝任能力
Friends. They'll respectfully question Conway's ability to serve.
然后在晚間新聞中
And then in the nightly news,
會有退休軍人權利活動家爭取更好的醫療
we'll have veteran rights activists arguing for better care.
很好
Good.
先生  計劃先打擊州長
Sir, the plan is to go after the governor first,
等將軍出面維護他
and when the general comes to his defense,
我們再用他抗命的錄音扳倒他
we use his hot mic comments to take him down, too.
祝賀你  先生
Congratulations, sir.
我想第一個祝賀你
I wanted to be the first to say it.
我們還得走競選流程
We still have to campaign.
沒錯  但您會勝選
Yeah, but you're going to win.
我們會的  道格
We are, Doug.
我們會的
We are.
俗世煩惱啊  散去吧
Common woe, be done.
各種各樣的兄弟會組織在歐美國家有著悠久的歷史
其中最廣為人知  同時也是同美國總統聯系最多的是"共濟會"
共濟會成立于18世紀的英格蘭  組織神秘  對會員遴選嚴格
會員中有許多政客  藝術家  科學家
如莫扎特  馬克·吐溫  發明青霉素的弗萊明等  都是共濟會會員
傳至美國后  同美國建國的歷史一直有著千絲萬縷的聯系
在簽署獨立宣言的55人中  有9名共濟會會員
而迄今為止的45任美國總統里  有15名是共濟會會員  達三分之一
(其中林登·約翰遜沒能完成晉級程序  未成為正式會員
所以有的統計沒將他算上  認為只有14名總統真正是共濟會會員)
共濟會發展至今  更多是一個社交性的社會組織
但其組織嚴守秘密  公眾對其所知甚少  因而衍生出不少駭人聽聞的傳說
包括這個組織怎樣影響和控制了世界  其實這些說法幾乎沒有任何根據
進入2017年后  美國媒體對俄羅斯在北極的擴張非常關注
目前普京正在對北極附近的俄羅斯軍事基地
進行冷戰結束后最大規模的擴張  而美國政府在這方面的動作相對落后
由于北極有著4千億桶的原油儲備  而被世界上幾個大國看作戰略要地
俄羅斯目前有40艘破冰船  其中6艘是核動力驅動
而美國只有2艘  其中1艘還不能工作
美國新任國防部長馬蒂斯在出席自己的任命聽證會時表示
美國不應該把北極的控制權拱手讓給其他國家